<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
  ~ Copyright © 2025 Museum für Naturkunde Berlin.
  ~ This code is licensed under MIT license (see LICENSE.txt for details)
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="accessibility">Accessibility</string>
    <string name="accessibility_timestamp">Status: April 2025; Android Version 4.1.31</string>
    <string name="accessibility_statement">The Naturblick app is intended to be accessible to as many people as possible – regardless of physical or cognitive limitations. We strive to meet the accessibility requirements set out in the Berlin Accessible ICT Act (BIKTG Bln) and the EU Directive 2016/2102.\n\nIn November 2024, the app was reviewed by the Berlin Monitoring Body for Digital Accessibility. The result: the app currently does not fully comply with accessibility requirements. Numerous barriers exist, particularly for screen reader users, people with visual impairments, and in the use of audio content.\n\nWe are working on gradually improving accessibility, including:\n\n&#8226; Adding alternative texts for images and buttons\n\n&#8226; Optimizing app navigation for assistive technologies\n\nAn action plan to address the deficiencies has been developed and is being continuously updated.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_report_problem">If you notice any barriers or have suggestions, we welcome your message.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_complete_report">You can find the full accessibility statement <a href="https://www.museumfuernaturkunde.berlin/de/erklaerung-zur-barrierefreiheit">here</a>.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_german_sign_language">Information in German Sign Language (DGS)</string>
    <string name="accessibility_german_sign_language_info">Currently, the Naturblick app does not offer content in German Sign Language (DGS). Providing information in DGS is not a mandatory requirement under current accessibility standards but is recommended under §3(4) BIKTG Bln as part of the highest possible accessibility standard.\n\nWe plan to include a sign language video explaining key features of the app in the future. Implementation will take place in close cooperation with experts in accessible communication.\n\nAs soon as DGS content becomes available, we will inform you here.</string>
</resources>