<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright © 2024 Museum für Naturkunde Berlin.
  ~ This code is licensed under MIT license (see LICENSE.txt for details)
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="help_how_to_use_title">How can I use Naturblick?</string>
    <string name="help_how_to_use">Take photos of plants and identify them with our automatic image recognition. Record bird sounds and identify which bird is singing with automatic sound recognition. Identify animals and plants by characteristics with our identification keys. Save and share your observations. Or learn more about species in the species portraits.</string>
    <string name="help_image_id_title">Plant recognition</string>
    <string name="help_image_id">Your photos of plants will be identified by pattern recognition. For the pattern recognition a quadratic image crop is used. You can adjust the image crop by moving the square or dragging it smaller/larger. With the button \"submit\" you send the cropped image to the servers of the Museum für Naturkunde Berlin. The selected section is then compared with the photos of all trained plant species by the algorithm of our partner Pl@ntNet and checked for similarities. The identification works best when there is a high similarity to the photo situation and quality of the training material (e.g. plants in the outdoors).\n\nWe display the most probable results of the pattern recognition. However, only species that have been trained can be recognized. It can therefore happen that your image shows a similarity with the trained photos, but none of the suggested species is correct.\n\nIf there is no sufficient match with the trained plant species or if the algorithm cannot recognize a plant in the image, we will display \"We could not identify a plant\".\n\nAn overview of the trained species can be found <a href="https://naturblick.museumfuernaturkunde.berlin/plantrecognition?lang=en">here</a>.\n\nMore information about Pl@ntNet can be found <a href="https://plantnet.org/en/about/">here</a>.</string>
    <string name="help_sound_id_title">Sound recognition</string>
    <string name="help_sound_id">The white box is used for sound recognition. You can adjust the section by moving the square or dragging it smaller/wider. Please select a section that best represents the animal\'s sound. Our pattern recognition gives the best results for recordings that are under 10 seconds. With the button \"submit\" you send the section to the servers of the Museum für Naturkunde Berlin for automatic identification.\n\nWe display the most probable results of the pattern recognition. However, only species that have been trained can be recognized. It can therefore happen that your recording shows a similarity with the trained recordings, but none of the suggested species is correct.\n\nIf there is no sufficient match with the trained animal species or if the algorithm cannot recognize an animal in the recording, we will display \"We could not identify an animal\".\n\n The algorithm was developed in cooperation with BirdID. It was trained with recordings of mammals, birds, amphibians and orthoptera. The list of species that can be identified can be found <a href="https://naturblick.museumfuernaturkunde.berlin/animalrecognition?lang=en">here</a>.</string>
    <string name="help_character_id_title">Identify with characteristics</string>
    <string name="help_character_id">In our identification tools, you can choose which characteristics you want to select. Simply skip all characteristics that you cannot determine. In the short explanation text for each characteristic, you will find information if more than one answer can be selected. A list shows all the species that are possible based on your selection.</string>
    <string name="help_fieldbook_title">Fieldbook</string>
    <string name="help_fieldbook">Your observations are stored in the fieldbook and can be edited by you. You can also manually set or improve the location of your observation on the map. Scroll and zoom the map to place the pin at the location. You can add more observations using the plus symbol at the bottom right.</string>
</resources>