<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
  ~ Copyright © 2025 Museum für Naturkunde Berlin.
  ~ This code is licensed under MIT license (see LICENSE.txt for details)
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="privacy_notice">Privacy notice</string>
    <string name="privacy_notice_intro">1. Introduction</string>
    <string name="privacy_notice_intro_text">When using Naturblick, personal data is collected and stored in databases. We consistently abide by data protection regulations when processing the data collected.</string>
    <string name="privacy_notice_responsible">2. Name and address of the controller responsible for data processing and contact data of the data protection officer</string>
    <string name="privacy_notice_responsible_text">Processing of personal data is the responsibility of:\n\nMuseum für Naturkunde Berlin\nInvalidenstr. 43\n10115 Berlin\n\nProf. Johannes Vogel, PhD, Director General\nPhone: +49 30 889140 - 8544\nEmail: johannes.vogel@mfn.berlin\n\nStephan Junker, Managing Director\nTel.: +49 30 889140 - 8330\nEmail: stephan.junker@mfn.berlin\n\nData protection officer of the Museum für Naturkunde:\nPhone: +49 30 889140 - 8440\nEmail: datenschutz@mfn.berlin</string>
    <string name="privacy_notice_use">3. Use and Disclosure of Personal Data</string>
    <string name="privacy_notice_use_text"><b>Log Data:</b>\n\nWhen using the Naturblick app, usage data relevant to data protection and data security is stored in a log file. Depending on the access protocol used, the log file may include the following information:\n&#8226; Audio and image recordings\n&#8226; Observation metadata (species name, geographic coordinates, time, quantity, notes)\n&#8226; Crash reports (stack traces, type of crash, trends, device and software version)\n&#8226; Device ID and metadata related to identification results (coordinates, time, identification history)\n&#8226; Anonymous usage data (information about your interactions with the app)\n&#8226; Event data (details of specific user actions, such as clicking buttons)\n&#8226; Device data (information about your device, including device type, operating system, and screen resolution)\n\nThe data collected is used exclusively for scientific purposes and is deleted once it is no longer needed. The extent of data collection may also be partially determined by technical requirements. No user profiles are created. The analysis is carried out by authorized staff members of the Museum für Naturkunde Berlin. Usage data is stored separately from any personal data provided by the user. No unauthorized disclosure of data to third parties takes place. Disclosure to government authorities occurs only in accordance with mandatory legal provisions or in the event of attacks on our systems for the purpose of criminal prosecution.\n\n<b>Real Names:</b>\n\nUsers are free to provide a name to be listed as the author of media and observations. The use of real names is optional and entirely voluntary. Observations (species name, geographic coordinates, time, quantity) and media are published under the terms of the CC BY-SA 4.0 license, as outlined in the terms of use. In accordance with this license, observation data and media are shared and published only in connection with the specified author name. After legal and content review, observations and media are shared with scientific projects and published on the Naturblick map.\n\n<b>Email Address:</b>\n\nTo register an account, we require your email address. Registration is only completed once you click the confirmation link sent to you by email. Your email address is used solely for account administration purposes. Registration is voluntary and can be withdrawn at any time. Your personal data (email address) will be deleted from our system upon account deletion. Data processing complies with all applicable data protection regulations. Your entries are transmitted in encrypted form. The Museum für Naturkunde Berlin applies technical and organizational measures consistent with current standards to protect your data against loss, manipulation, or unauthorized access.</string>
</resources>