<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="new_tac_greeting">We are excited you are interested in learning more about your area\'s nature.</string>
    <string name="new_tac_info">We give you an overview of the terms of use and data collection.</string>
    <string name="new_tac_authorship_title">Authorship of image and sound recordings, observations with geo-coordinates</string>
    <string name="new_tac_authorship">All recordings (images and sound recordings, observations with geo-coordinates) made with Naturblick are licensed under <a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/">CC BY-SA 4.0</a>, i.e. they may be distributed and used under the terms of Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike.
</string>
    <string name="new_tac_change_authorship">If you wish, you can indicate your authorship with a name. The recordings will then be published together with this name. All images that do not have an author\'s name will be published under MfN_Naturblick. You can find more information in settings.</string>
    <string name="new_tac_data_collection_title">Overview of data collection</string>
    <string name="new_tac_data_collection">All data is collected for academic purposes only. As soon as the data is no longer needed, we delete it. Which data is collected and to what extent may also partly result from technical necessities. When using this app, the following data is collected and stored anonymously on the servers of the Museum für Naturkunde in Berlin:</string>
    <string name="new_tac_data_collection_sound_and_image_title">Sound and image recordings</string>
    <string name="new_tac_data_collection_sound_and_image">The app uses the phone\'s microphone and camera for the automated species identification service. The recordings are stored anonymously and used, for example, as training material for pattern recognition. If you wish, you can enter an author name for the recordings/images you generate. This data is also used for quality assurance and confirmation of observations. You can find out more about how and why observations are checked on <a href="https://naturblick.museumfuernaturkunde.berlin/map?lang=en">the map of our Naturblick platform</a>.</string>
    <string name="new_tac_data_collection_metadata_title">Metadata of the observation (species name, geo-coordinates, time, number, notes)</string>
    <string name="new_tac_data_collection_metadata">The app needs access to your location to record metadata on coordinates and time. Time and location information is an important basis for validating observations in biodiversity research.  However, you can also use the app without your location. You can add the number of observations and other notes about your observation yourself, providing additional valuable information. This data is used <a href="https://naturblick.museumfuernaturkunde.berlin/map?lang=en">when checking observations</a> and is passed on to scientific projects.</string>
    <string name="new_tac_crashreports_title">Crashreports</string>
    <string name="new_tac_crashreports">We collect automatic crash reports with stack traces, origin of crash, trends and version of the mobile device operating system to identify and elimintate software bugs.</string>
    <string name="new_tac_data_collection_instrument_id_title">Device ID and metadata of the observation results (coordinates, time, observation history)</string>
    <string name="new_tac_data_collection_instrument_id1">Your anonymised identification results and the use of the identification tools we have developed are scientifically evaluated. Based on this, the app will be further developed and improved on the one hand, and the effectiveness of the tools we have developed will be examined on the other.</string>
    <string name="new_tac_data_collection_instrument_id2">The app needs authorisation to access the phone (phone status and identity) in order to read the device ID. This is sent to our server in encrypted form so that we do not have any information about the unencrypted device ID. This enables us to scientifically evaluate the use of the app without user registration (LogIn) and without having to collect further data. In our interdisciplinary team, we research and develop digital tools for the urban experience of nature. <a href="https://naturblick.museumfuernaturkunde.berlin/about?lang=en">Learn more about us</a>.</string>
    <string name="new_tac_account_title">Account</string>
    <string name="new_tac_account">You can save your observations across several mobile devices and display them on all connected mobile phones with a Naturblick account. We need your e-mail address for registration. Your e-mail address will only be used for the administration of the account. Registration/login is voluntary and can be revoked at any time. Your personal data will be deleted from our system when the account is deleted. You can still use Naturblick without an account.</string>
    <string name="new_tac_data_collection_summary">Data protection is very important to us. You can find more information about data protection <a href="https://www.museumfuernaturkunde.berlin/de/datenschutzerklaerung">here</a> and in the imprint of Naturblick.</string>
    <string name="new_tac_questions">If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us: <a href="mailto:naturblick@mfn.berlin">naturblick@mfn.berlin</a></string>
    <string name="new_tac_usage_is_acceptance">By using Naturblick you agree to our terms and conditions.</string>
</resources>